<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ScreenshotData>
	<Group Name="Icarus">
		<Screenshot>
			<FileName>ssIcarus</FileName>
			<AltText>Gallio's Icarus GUI Runner</AltText>
			<Description>Gallio's Icarus GUI Runner displays the results of running a sample MbUnit test assembly.</Description>
		</Screenshot>

		<Screenshot>
			<FileName>ssIcarus2</FileName>
			<AltText>Gallio's Icarus GUI Runner</AltText>
			<Description>Gallio's Icarus Runner displaying the Gallio Test Report results.</Description>
		</Screenshot>		
	
		<Screenshot>
			<FileName>ssInstallOptions</FileName>
			<AltText>Gallio's Icarus GUI Runner</AltText>
			<Description>Gallio supports many frameworks, tools and runners as seen by the components available in the installer.</Description>
		</Screenshot>
	</Group>

	<Group Name="Echo">
		<Screenshot>
			<FileName>EchoCommandLine</FileName>
			<AltText>Running tests from command line using Echo.</AltText>
			<Description>Gallio.Echo.exe is a command line test runner. It has a progress monitor which gives you feedback about the status of a test run. Additionally, it allows you to specify the destination and format (say xml, mht, etc.) of your results. Use plugins to generate customized reports and charts.</Description>
		</Screenshot>
	</Group>

	<Group Name="VisualStudio Integration">
		<Screenshot>
			<FileName>VisualStudioIntegration</FileName>
			<AltText>Running tests in visual studio.</AltText>
			<Description>Gallio's test runner is integrated in to visual studio. When you open any test inside visual studio it presents you a green and yellow circle adjacent to test. Left-Click to open up a pane which presents you a list of actions. Apart from running/debugging a test, it allows you to create sessions of tests from different fixtures. These sessions can be stored and you can run them.</Description>
		</Screenshot>
		<Screenshot>
			<FileName>VisualStudioIntegrationGallioReport</FileName>
			<AltText>Gallio report inside visual studio.</AltText>
			<Description>When you run a test inside visual studio, the results are displayed in a new window pane. This window has a button to display condensed/full test report. When selected it displays the test results in a new tab right inside visual studio. Note that the exceptions box has clickable links which navigate directly to the displayed location right inside visual studio!!!</Description>
		</Screenshot>
	</Group>
</ScreenshotData>