<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Gallio Automation Platform</title>
    <link>http://www.gallio.org</link>
    <description>News and information about the Gallio Automation Platform for .NET</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 14:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gallio Alpha 3 Update 1 Released</title>
      <link>http://www.gallio.org</link>
      <description>
        Today we released a small update to the Alpha 3 Release.  This release makes the MbUnit TestFixture attribute optional and 
        fixed a couple minor bugs.
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 04:32:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallio Alpha 3 Released</title>
      <link>http://www.gallio.org</link>
      <description>
        Today we released Gallio Alpha 3 with enhancements and bug fixes. Of particular interest is support for MSTest, experimental Visual 
        Studio Team System integration, annotations, report improvements and data binding enhancements. --- More details are available 
        at: http://blog.bits-in-motion.com/2008/05/announcing-gallio-v30-alpha-3.html.
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 09:54:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallio's Jeff Brown part of discussion on Hanselminutes</title>
      <link>http://www.hanselminutes.com/default.aspx?showID=130</link>
      <description>
        Scott Hanselman recorded a great interview at ALT.Net Seattle with Brad Wilson, Charlie Poole, Roy Osherove and Jeff Brown. Among 
        other things, we talk about Gallio and the work we are doing to foster innovation and recognize diversity within the .Net testing 
        community. --- The Past, Present and Future of .NET Unit Testing Frameworks. http://www.hanselminutes.com/default.aspx?showID=130
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 06:38:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallio Book Chapter 3 now on gallio.org</title>
      <link>http://www.gallio.org/BookTemporary.aspx</link>
      <description>
        Gallio Book:  Chapter 3 "Getting Started" added to www.gallio.org today.  The Gallio project is creating an online book about using 
        Gallio.  This book is a separate undertaking from the Gallio API Documentation that is also in the works.
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 16:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallio.org adds RSS Feed</title>
      <link>http://www.gallio.org</link>
      <description>Gallio.org the official website of the Gallio Automation Platform today added an RSS feed to its website www.gallio.org.  
      The feed will include news items about releases and other items of import relating to Gallio, including updates to the website 
      and any blogs or articles of note.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Brown blogs about Gallio v3 Alpha 2</title>
      <link>http://blog.bits-in-motion.com/2008/03/announcing-gallio-v30-alpha-2.html</link>
      <description>"Today we have released Gallio v3.0 Alpha 2, including a preview of MbUnit v3.  There's been a ton of work behind the scenes to 
      provide a compelling model for data-driven testing.  Here's an example of this feature in action.  Notice the use of generic method parameters.  
      Also notice that we perform an automatic string to DateTime conversion and that we take some care in how we format the parameters for 
      presentation in the test results..."  Read more at Jeff's blog...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 09:57:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallio Alpha 2 released.</title>
      <link>http://www.gallio.org</link>
      <description>Today we released Alpha 2. New features include MbUnit data-binding, the complete realization of the Gallio test model, and 
      integrated support for ReSharper, PowerShell, NCover, TypeMock, Pex and ASP.NET MVC. Continued improvements to Echo, Icarus, the installer, 
      and all other tools are also a part of this release.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 12:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallio.org launches on the web</title>
      <link>http://www.gallio.org</link>
      <description>The Gallio Project, an open-source Automation Platform for .NET launched it's official website today.  News and information 
      about the Gallio Automation Platform is available on the website.  The site also features a convenient "out toolbar" that provide quick 
      access to various Gallio Project development resources, such as the google-code repository and wiki, as well as the gallio-dev google group site.  
      Over the next few months a full API reference will be added, as well as turorials and articles.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
